Guide to the Stanford University, Information Technology Services, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1985-104
  - ASPPG (Administrative Systems Policy & Planning Group) 1973-75 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Audit: General 1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Audit: General 1971-77 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Audit: Academic Computing 7/17/1970 - 9/14/1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Audit: Administrative Computing 7/68 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Audit: CIT 5/15/1980 - 4/16/1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Audit: DCAA 11/10/67 - 8/12/1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Audit: Medical Computing 9/12/1973 - 4/24/1974 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Audit: Auto CD Computer System 1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - BALLOTS: 168 Conversion 1975-76 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - BALLOTS: Miscellaneous 1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - BALLOTS: Sanders CRT Selection and Design 1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - BALLOTS: Initial "BALLOTS III" Development Plans 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - BALLOTS: Notes, Phil Long Visit 7/1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - BALLOTS: National Library Network Memoranda, Papers 5/10/1977 - 11/1/1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - BALLOTS: Selection and Installation of Sanders CRT Terminals 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - BALLOTS: Center Working File Fall 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - BALLOTS 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - BALLOTS: Advisory Committee Minutes 4/26/1977 - 5/20/1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - BALLOTS: Advisory Committee 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - BALLOTS: SU Response to RLG RFP for an Automated Bibliographic Control System (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - BALLOTS: Proposals 4/1/1970 - 10/4/1977 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - BALLOTS: Grants 2/9/1970 - 5/31/1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - BALLOTS: Computing Budgets 4/25/1975 - 12/16/1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - BALLOTS: UC Berkeley Agreement, Business Plan 3/16/1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - BALLOTS: Executive Committee Meeting 10/1974 -2/24/1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: Weber Briefings 1/27/1978 - 11/21/1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Budget: CIT 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Budget: Administrative Computing- Student Services 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Budget: Administrative Computing- Business and Finance 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Budget: Administrative Computing 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Budget: Administrative Computing 1976-77 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Budget: Administrative Data Processing 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Budget: Campus Facility 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Budget: Campus Facility 1977-78 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Budget: Campus Facility 1976-77 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Budget: Campus Facility 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Budget: LOTS 4/7/1975 - 10/17/1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Budget: Medical Computing 1977-78 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Budget: Medical Computing 1976-77 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Budget: CIT 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Budget: SCIP 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Budget: SCIP 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Budget: SCIP 1977-78 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Budget: SCIP 1976-77 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Budget: RLIN 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Budget: Rates 1977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Budget: Hank Epstein 7/1/1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Budget: Miscellaneous Document Drafts 1/24/1978 - 3/16/1978 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Budget: Cost Studies 12/16/1971 - 7/26/1972 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Budget: SLAC 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Building Dedications: Forsythe 12/29/1979 - 1/7/1980 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Business and Finance: Datapoint Equipment 8/1/1978 - 8/31/1979 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Business and Finance: Data Processing 3/8/1979 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Business and Finance: Senior Staff 1981 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Business and Finance: Senior Staff 1982-83 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Business and Finance: Career Planning and Placement 12/27/1979 - 1/30/1980 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University IBM Project 1/3/1983 - 5/31/1983 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - CCLN (Council for Computerized Library Networks) 1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Budget 12/17/1979 - 11/18/1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Computer Center 10/17/1977 - 8/1/1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Monthly Management Reports 1/1977 - 5/1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nat Dickmeyer Meeting 4/6/1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - SCIP Computing Fund Usage 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Payroll Personnel System (PPS) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Invoices and Billings 1/21/1979 - 6/1/1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Audit: Data Security Controls Report 2/13/1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Tape Statistics Presentation 5/8/1980 - 9/25/1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - CENTREX 3/9/1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education 9/30/1980 - 10/15/1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - CIT: Development 12/11/1979 -11/24/1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - CIT: Directors Meetings 5/9/1980 - 7/21/1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - CIT: Directors Meeting 6/17/1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - CIT: COST Centers 1981-82 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - CIT: Budget 1981-82 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - CIT: Budget Protocol 10/2/1979 - 12/12/1979 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Information Systems Planning Working File 3/12/1981 - 3/18/1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Director's Staff Agendas 6/13/1978 - 5/6/1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Director's Staff Agendas 5/6/1980 -1/5/1981 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Director's Staff Agendas 1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Director's Staff Agendas 1975-78 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - CIT: Miscellaneous 2/15/1980 - 9/16/1980 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - CIT: Personnel 10/15/1979 - 12/30/1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - CIT: Presentations 12/26/1979 - 3/21/1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - CIT: Symposium on Office Automation 2/25/1980 - 3/20/1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - 3033 12/28/1978 - 4/3/1981 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - 3303, 2nd Processor; IBM 370/168 2/12/1980 - 9/29/1980 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 3800 Printer Carcinogen Danger 10/16/1980 - 10/28/1980 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - 9700 Printer 2/12/1980 -8/17/1981 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - COFHE 4/25/1977 - 8/2/1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Management Development Program (MDP) 2/23/1981 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Business and Finance: Directors 5/5/1981 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - TFM (Terminals for Managers) Contact 8/5/1981 - 9/2/1981 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Director's Office Personnel 8/27/1980 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Avenue A 8/25/1981 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Computing and Information Technology Group: Academic Council Committee on Computing and Computer Science 4/10/1981 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Director’s Staff 7/13/1981 - 8/25/1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Planning Research Group 7/14/1981 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - CAUSE 1981 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - TFM Contact Steering Committee 2/20/1981 - 3/31/1982 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - NSI Governance Group 9/10/1981 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Business and Finance: Data Processing Steering Committee 7/19/1981 - 10/22/1981 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - LOTS Computer Facility Committee 6/24/1981 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - U.S. House of Representatives: House Information Systems Committee 6/1981 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Administrative Council 10/1981 - 11/1981 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - WASC Review 5/14/1981 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Library Council - Stanford University 3/2/1981 -7/16/1981 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Business and Finance: Data Processing Steering Committee 6/8/1981 - 7/9/1981 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Business and Finance: Senior Staff Minutes 8/2/1981 - 11/5/1980 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Hospital Patient Accounting Project Steering Committee Meeting 8/12/1980 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Business and Finance: Senior Staff 11/6/1980 - 5/6/1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Committees: Committee on Investment Responsibility 12/30/1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Committees: Committee on Computation Facilities 7/23/1975 - 3/16/1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Committees: Committee on Computers in Education 2/17/1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Committees: Stanford/Palo Alto Liaison Committee 4/1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Committees: A21 Project Steering Committee 12/11/1979 - 9/2/1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Committees: A21 Project Definitions Study Group 6/6/1979 - 1/16/1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Committees: Academic Council on Computing and Information Systems 1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Committees: A21 Project Facilities/Space Study Group 9/27/1979 - 10/3/1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Committees: A21 Project Technical Advisory Committee (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Committees: 3033 Installation Task Force 9/4/1980 - 10/7/1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Committees: Academic Working Group (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Committees: Ad Hoc SLAC Computer Facility Review 4/14/1971 - 7/26/1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Committees: ACS 10/26/1977 - 4/10/1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Committees: Administrative Computing Subcommittee 3/20/1975 -1/1978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Committees: ATL Task Force 11/1979 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Committees: Ad Hoc Computer Terminal Advisory Group (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Committees: BALLOTS Center Advisory Board 12/7/1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Committees: Board of Trustees 12/8/1977 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Committees: PAC 10/25/68 - 6/22/1981 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Committees: PAC 10/26/1971 - 3/12/1981 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Committees: BALLOTS/Campus Steering Committee 5/22/1978 - 9/8/1978 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Committees: Centrex Replacement 2/13/1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Committees: Communications Network 1/15/ 79 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Committees: CONTEXT Implementation Team 4/10/1981 - 5/1/1981 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Committees: Computation Facility Committee 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Committees: Computer Policy Committee 5/16/1978 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Committees: Privacy Panel 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Committees: Management Advisory Group 1/16/1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Committees: Management Advisory Group 4/10/1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Committees: COST (Committee on Office Systems and Technology) 10/12/1978 - 5/8/1979 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Committees: New Building and Steering Committee 9/27/1978 - 9/13/1979 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Committees: Tape Task Force 3/1980 - 3/23/1981 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Committees: Research and Instruction Subcommittee 8/10/1973 - 3/26/1975 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Committees: Joint Subcommittee on Faculty/Staff Housing 11/17/1978 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Committees: Provost's Computer Committee 11/4/1970 - 8/16/1973 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Committees: Privacy Panel 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Committees: Privacy Panel 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Committees: SCIP/SLAC Separation 7/31/1978 - 2/8/1979 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Committees: Vice Presidents Group -Troika 4/25/1980 - 3/4/1981 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Committees: Task Force on the Future of Computing at Stanford: Background Material 1978 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Committees: Union Contract 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - DARPA Proposal 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Computer Acquisitions 3/18/1982 - 5/6/1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Computer Acquisitions 5/7/1982 - 10/6/1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Computers: Inventory of Hardware/Software 7/14/1977 - 8/18/1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Computers: Inventory 6/1977 - 8/1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Computer Performance Evaluation and Planning Committee 1/10/1981 - 12/28/1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Consultants: R.L. Patrick 10/20/69 - 9/13/1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Consultants: Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. 7/16/1979 - 8/24/1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Consultants: “Issues Facing SCIP” Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. 3/1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Consultants: Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. 7/1976 -9/27/1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Consultants: Input, Inc. 2/1980 - 5/20/1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Consultants: Rich Levitt 1/10/1979 - 1/29/1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Consultants: Ari Ollikainen 1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Consultants: Philip Long 7/9/1975 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Consultants: Gerald F Miller 11/4/1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Consultants: Kevin Kay 3/17/1976 -6/16/1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Consultants: Ty Johnston 4/8/1970 - 6/23/1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Consultants: Hank Epstein 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Consultants: C.H. Hitchner Jr. 11/23/1970 - 4/15/1971 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Consultants: Rod Fredrickson 5/19/1970 - 7/10/1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Consultants: David E. Cummins 8/27/1970 - 11/4/1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Consultants: Brett Butler 1/3/1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Consultants: Jesse Caton 3/10/1975 - 8/26/1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Consultants: Lennie Stoyel 1/11/1976 - 4/11/1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Consultants: Dan Rose 5/17/1976 - 12/28/1978 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Consultants: Peggy Riebman 7/19/1976 - 8/16/1976 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Consultants: General 4/10/1970 - 4/3/1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Consultants: Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. 9/1/1981 - 7/8/1982 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Computer Science Department/CIT Relations 2/2/1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Computer Science Department 11/1/67 - 8/14/1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Computer Science Department 2/10/1982 - 5/10/1982 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Proposal: Expansion of the Computing Center Facility 1975 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Agreements: EDUCOM - Business and Finance Study 9/27/1978 - 9/4/1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Agreements: TERADATA "Partnership" 8/27/1981 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - SCIP Director’s Office Correspondence Filing Index (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - CIT-AIS Computer Accounts 11/1/1981 - 12/16/1981 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - CONTEXT Advisory Council 10/1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Portfolio Approach to Information Systems 10/1981 - 11/1981 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Administrative Council 11/18/1981 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Rosters: Preliminary Edition 9/23/1981 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - OBS: Jeff Stein 9/3/1981 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Computer Systems and Services 12/21/1981 - 7/19/1983 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - XA conversion 12/2/1983 - 6/14/1983 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 3083 Implementation Team 6/27/1983 - 8/15/1983 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Interactive Rates on 3081 Node 12/7/1982 - 12/16/1982 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - TFM Evaluation – Electronic Messaging 3/17/1982 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Computer Camps 11/18/1981 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - 3081 Rates 8/2/1982 - 7/27/1983 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - 3083 Implementation (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Consultants: General 2/4/1980 -9/2/1980 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Consultants: Peat, Marwick, Mitchell, and Co. 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Consultants: Coopers and Lybrand 1/9/1978 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - RLG: Arms Report 3/18/1982 - 4/26/1982 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - CONTEXT 1/29/1981 - 7/10/1981 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - CONTEXT Implementation Team 4/10/1981 - 7/8/1981 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Controller's Office 5/9/1980 - 7/7/1980 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Contracts: Alyeska Pipeline 10/8/1974 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Contracts: Computer Synthetics TESDATA 8/4/1970 - 5/24/1978 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Contracts: California State Department of Education 9/27/1977 - 10/13/1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Contracts: Department of Food and Agriculture 10/29/1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: California State Department of Health 7/1/1981 - 2/7/1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Development - Intel 7/29/1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Fujitsu 9/24/1979 - 10/7/1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: IBM Joint Study 10/10/1978 - 10/29/18 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Contracts: IBM/SCIP Professional Exchange 1/13/1976 - 9/9/1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Medical Center 1/29/1973 - 10/22/1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Sale of 3033 and 3350 8 Modules 11/1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: Napa College 8/20/60 - 11/4/1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: RLIN 2/1979 - 3/1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Sales of 158/67/145 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: RLG/RLIN 12/13/1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: SLAC Agreements 2/10/1970 - 5/18/1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Contracts: Solar Energy Research Institute 2/27/1978 - 10/11/1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Contracts: Santa Clara User Agreement 1/13/69 - 12/19/1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Contracts: US Government - Flexible Pricing MOU 10/9/67 - 9/15/1980 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Contracts: U.S. Geological Survey 1975 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Contracts: Veterans Administration Medical Center 9/1/1981 - 9/13/1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Contracts: Xerox Agreements re: Ethernet 11/3/1980 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Contracts: Xerox Agreement re: Dolphin Computer 5/11/1981 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Ced Bennett - ADPS 11/7/1979 - 10/24/1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Copyright Law 1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Michael Carter 1/1/1980 - 5/17/1983 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Carolyn Lougee 4/14/1980 - 4/20/1980 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Paul Kaufman 7/1978 - 6/14/1983 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Jane Marcus 4/11/1980 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Linnea Marenco 7/30/1981 - 10/1/1981 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Edna Nigh 10/21/1980 - 12/4/1980 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Bob Nosanchuk - Operations 2/27/1980 - 9/9/1980 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Larry Rosen - Facility Accounting 12/7/1979 - 11/11/1980 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Mike Roberts 10/22/1979 -12/21/1980 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Jon Sandelin 6/1/1980 - 10/29/1980 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - BALLOTS/RLIN: Campus Facility Steering Committee 1978 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Jeannie Siegman 1/11/1980 - 10/27/1980 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Edward E. Shaw - CIT Directors and Managers 9/3/1980 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Ruth Short - Applications Manager 10/27/1980 - 10/30/1980 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Ed Williams 2/1/1980 - 4/29/1981 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Bill Yundt 6/6/1980 - 5/31/1983 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - CORE Project 2/22/1982 - 5/13/1983 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, General 10/17/1980 - 7/10/1981 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - COST 4/1980 - 7/1980 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Center for Research on Women 11/28/1973 - 11/18/1977 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Data Base Management 6/1979 - 2/23/1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Data Base Management Selection Group 2/15/1980 - 8/22/1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Data Communications 12/10/1979 - 2/13/1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Data Processing Steering Committee 6/17/1980 - 11/26/1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Digital Equipment Corporation (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Simulation and Gaming Project for Inter- Institutional Computer Networking 9/1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - EDSHAW/SAMS 10/25/1977 - 11/13/1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - EDUCOM: EDUNET 5/13/1980 - 11/25/1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - EDUCOM 10/2/1979 - 2/20/1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - EDUCOM: Information Technologies and Computing at Stanford: Dimensions and Facets 1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - EDUCOM: Strategic Planning Meeting 6/1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - EDUCOM: Board of Trustees Meeting 6/22/1983 - 6/23/1983 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - EDUCOM: Committees 1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - EDUCOM 6/15/1977 - 9/12/1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - EDUCOM: Conference 11/15/1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - EDUCOM: Conference 10/19-21/1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - EDUCOM: Business and Finance Report 8/10/1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - EDUCOM: EDUNET 1981 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - EDUCOM: Board of Trustees Meeting 1/26/1983 - 1/27/1983 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - EDUCOM: Board of Trustees Meeting 6/28/1982 -6/29/1982 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - EDUCOM: Board of Trustees Meeting 1/27/1982 - 1/28/1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - EDUCOM: Board of Trustees 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - EDUCOM: Council 1981-82 annual Report (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - EDUCOM: EDUNET 1982 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Engineering Services Group 1/2/1970 - 5/25/1978 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - EDUCOM: SPIRES (Stanford Public Information Retrieval System) Consortium Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - SPIRES Consortium 10/27/1982 - 7/26/1983 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - UNIX 8/26/1981 - 4/14/1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence & Memoranda, General 12/1/1982 - 7/27/1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - CIT: A Guide to Services 5/1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Acquisitions: Facilities and Equipment 5/8/1981 - 9/3/1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Computing - Miscellaneous 12/6/1977 - 5/8/1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - University Computing Funds 12/13/1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Financial Correspondence 1/12/1978 - 8/18/1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Facilities: Building and Space 1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Facilities: Building and Space - General 1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Facilities: Building and Space - General 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Facilities: Building and Space - Forsythe Hall 3/21/1978 - 6/8/1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Facilities: Building and Space - SLAC 12/1973 - 8/29/1976 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Facilities: Power Sources 12/23/68 - 5/3/1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Facilities: Computer Power Supplies - Group 2A Utility (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Facilities: Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1977 to 1982 5/1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Fiber Optic Transmission System 6/1979 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Finance: Sales Tax 1983 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Finance: Financial Economic Models - SCIP 1978 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Finance: Capital Funds 3/30/1972 - 10/13/1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Finance: Corporate Funds 3/30/1973 - 11/13/1980 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Finance: Loans and Interests 8/9/1973 - 3/4/1981 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Finance: Financial Planning 1982 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Finance: “Financial Statement Analysis of Universities” Report 7/1979 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Finance: Funding Problems 9/10/65 - 10/25/1977 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Finance: Financial Reviews 1/6/1970 - 4/29/1974 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Forms: Invention Disclosures (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Forms: IBM Vendor Blanks 10/1976 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Forms: Vendor Contracts 1971-73 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Forsythe Highlight Reports 5/7/1979 - 7/30/1980 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Committees: Information Planning Systems Group 8/29/1980 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Gifts 1/6/1975 - 3/15/1983 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Governor Stanford Locomotive 1/31/1977 - 12/4/1980 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Governor Stanford Locomotive: California State Railroad Museum 9/29/1975 - 3/4/1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Governor Stanford Locomotive 12/20/1980 - 4/27/1981 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Governor Stanford Locomotive: California State Railroad Museum Interpretive Plan 7/1975 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Government Relations 7/18/67 - 4/9/1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Grants: Renewal proposal for Stanford Pilot Regional Educational Computing Network 7/1/68 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Grants: EDUCOM 6/20/1974 - 3/30/1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Grants: Government Guidelines 8/10/1970 - 6/25/1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Health and Safety 12/9/1971 -5/20/1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Tape Mount Rates 1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - PC for the Humanities Working File 5/26/1982 - 4/15/1983 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Micro Computer Program 6/30/1982 - 4/22/1983 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Computers and the Creative Process: A Study of the TIRO Project 8/18/1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - IBM 3/15/1982 - 7/18/1983 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Insurance 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Insurance 1969-1976 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Information Technology and Computing: Programs 9/14/1981 - 10/12/1981 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - IBM Systems Network Architecture Report 12/22/1980 - 5/7/1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Information & Data Base Publishing Reports 6/24/1980 - 1/30/1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Intel Corporation 6/7/1979 - 6/10/1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Inventory: Computer 8/8/1975 -8/5/1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Inventory: The SLAC Central Computer 10/25/1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Inventory: 370/168 Configuration - General 5/9/1975 - 11/3/1976 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Inventory: General 5/12/1970 - 11/1978 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Inventory: 3033 Configuration 8/12/1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Inventory: 370 Triplex Configuration 3/15/1976 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Inventory: Word Processors 2/4/1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Student Computing in the Coming Year 2/16/1982 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - DENDRAL Trailer 8/10/1982 - 9/2/1982 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - LOTS 12/8/1981 - 6/1/1982 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - “Opening Computer Accounts on LESS” 6/30/1981 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Articles: Miscellaneous 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Articles: Administrative Systems 7/1981 -8/1981 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Articles: Computer 3/1979 - 3/1980 (Box 11, Folder 28)